Yes, we get superpowers!
Superpowers!
There's a monster deep within your dreams.
Taking aim for your
heart so it would seem.
Stand tall and read, go to
hell and jump for paradise!
Every time dangerous, dangerous!
We like it serious, serious, oh!
Looking deep in the dream
there is the one in pain.
Turns out that's the one who
means the most to you today.
Adventure calls now, let's go!
The balls filled between
us, they will show.
Still what we don't know?
Yes, working hard together.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream.
Despite the rivalry?
Gotta see it through.
Believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
All the love and the tears.
In the world we're in.
United gently bringing up.
Our thought again, yeah.
We're the foolish ones
we love, we'll carry on.
Till we see the light, the sun will rise.
The greatest fight at its core
is against myself forevermore.
Come on, let's do it now, let's go!
The balls built between
us, they will show.
So what we don't know, that's
what we call adventure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Got to dream despite the rivalry.
Gotta see it through believing in you.
There's even charm in failure.
Yes, we've got superpowers.
Superpowers.
Yes, we're the superpowers.
Be careful, sir?
I can't believe this!
It seems she's turned
back to her own self.
Could Pudding's Cake have really been
that finger-licking lickety-good?
I've never seen her with such a
lickety blissful expression before.
Is she okay?
Mama, I need you to snap out of it.
I have to give you an
updated status report.
First of all, Buggy should
still be somewhere nearby.
I'm so happy.
She's not lickety listening.
Over there!
Hmm? Wait.
Hey, wait a second!
That ship, that's not the
Straw Hats vessel at all!
Impossible!
That vessel belongs to the Sun Pirates!
It can't be!
I thought it was a direct hit!
Did they switch places? Bastards!
Where the hell did the Straw Hats go?
Hurry up, Wadatsumi!
Carry them all to safety.
Are you sure?
This is the legendary ship
that Fisher Tiger made.
I'm certain.
Kill them! Get going!
There's no time left!
Huh? What?
Whoa!
You see them, guys?
Get in there, guys.
What the hell?
Where do we wind up?
Concealed in Waratsumi's mouth.
We're out of here.
They're underwater.
I knew I saw something!
It was the giant hairy baby!
All ships turn 180 degrees!
Scumbags, get back here!
Tropical torpedoes!
It's over!
There it is, Straw Hat's ship!
Whoa, don't die!
Fire!
And don't stop till they're sunk!
Just go on without me!
Straw Hat, I know I did a
bad thing on Fishman Island,
but I'm real sorry!
Thankfully, Boss Chief may still
let me tag along after that.
And I'll always be grateful.
Pain in the neck.
I'm coming after you.
Don't worry, Boss.
Ever since you told us you wanted to
join Straw Hat, we made up our minds.
We support you.
Mama's the type of person who will
kill anyone who tries to escape.
Sha-sha-sha!
You know what we have
to do then, right, guys?
We'll serve as Captain Jinbei's
shield and die in his place.
We can't all get killed!
Someone has to tell the story!
I can't deny that!
No judgment to those who back out.
But for those who are brave enough,
prepare yourselves for the worst.
Now we shall let these fools know,
no one can stop Jinbei's new voyage.
All of our minds were made up.
Maratsumi, get back!
Uh, lad, everyone's here?
Leave these guys to us.
Keep moving, Jinbei.
Don't worry.
We're sending you off with our blessings!
All right, men, let's do this! Onward!
Take it easy.
The ship's great weakness is flooding.
The water must be removed.
Before the situation worsens!.
The sun is getting heavy and slow?.
So, hatch up the hole in the sail and
find the proper angle to catch the wind.
You must work as fast as possible.
You're still several hours out
from leaving this territory.
Why are you spouting that junk?
Say what you mean.
Luffy.
I'm sorry.
I cannot bring myself to leave them.
Right. Gotcha.
We'll stay and help, too.
No.
I'll cover your backs
to ensure your safety.
If the mothership and its fleet remain
at our heels, escape will be impossible,
I'm certain.
I implore you, allow me to
stay and bring up the rear.
I shall return alive.
You have my solemn vow.
Just remember,
Team Bane, I'm your captain
now, so don't let me down!
I won't turn around.
I'll be waiting for you and Wano.
You better show up.
Luffy.
My deepest gratitude.
Jinbei!
Don't die no matter what! Got it?
please tell me someone took care
of that Straw Hat brat he's still
alive but he has nowhere left to hide
right about now my siblings should
be giving him the lickety-licking
of his life they have him near
cacao island if he's not confirmed
dead then i'll go finish him off let's
go dark spotted candy frog sorry
boy it's over i want your soul and
i'm gonna use it to make my most
powerful homies yet
we
scraped
through
with our lives looks like lady luck
was on our side now let's scram
while it's quiet I'm really a little
worried about Gemma knock it off
burn to death let's go
Are you alright, Aladdin?
Jinbei, staying after all? Not quite.
I'm still a member of the Strahlhats.
But in order to save my captain,
I must remain here and fight.
You must be pulling my fin.
What little faith you have in us, Jinbei?
Please don't think of it that way.
I'm ensuring your safety.
I'd like a proper send-off from everybody.
I know firsthand just
what you're capable of.
Let's use that tenacity to assist
with the Sunnies' escape, shall we?
Oh, Sherman!
Look over there!
Hurry, Brooke!
This is our big chance!
We need to move at full speed immediately!
Roger that, Nami!
When Fishman gets serious,
we're able to big currents!
Amazing! We'll see!
The sun is really speeding up now that
the fishmen shifted the tide for us.
I'll be waiting.
The Straw Hats are leaving Team Bay
behind, but they're getting away.
Our fleet's being pushed back by the tide.
I fear we'll lose sight
of their ship soon.
That's the stuffed Straw Hat.
Since when are you in his corner?
Well, it's because he's a contender!
What do you mean?
Oh, Stussy.
Don't play dumb with me.
The worst generation.
The Surgeon of Death, Trafalgar Law.
The Magician, Basil Hawkins.
Red Flag, Diaz, Drake.
The Roar of the Sea, Scratchman, Apu.
Capone, Gang, Boss.
The Glutton, Jewelry, Bonnie.
Mad Monk, Rougie.
Eustass, Captain Kidd.
The Massacre, Soldier, Killer.
Blackbeard Marshal D.
Teach and
Straw Hat Monkey D.
Luffy
In the near future.
One of the worst generation.
Will rise above the rest.
And take up the legendary mantle.
The next pirate king.
Lies amongst them.
I see.
What a shame.
So Pedro's dead.
My name's Pedro.
We need your help Duke
dog storm and master cat
viper are in need of
urgent medical assistance.
Both of their lives are at stake
in the world still needs them?
Above all else those two.
They must absolutely be saved!
Don't let them die!
I feel like this isn't where
you were supposed to die.
It's okay.
Don't beat yourself up.
Pedro acted of his own free will.
Please don't feel
responsible for it, alrighty?
You two guys saved the Mokumo dukedom.
So we wanted to repay our dead.
If it weren't for Pedro.
We'd have all died back there anyway.
So please
Just be thankful, okay?
It was for the best.
This is how it's supposed to be.
This is how he wanted it.
I understand I know how Pedro was.
Yeah!
Ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha! Soul focus!
Soul focus!
Echoes of the heart as we depart!
It weighs heavy on our mind,
the friends we left behind!
Let the tide take me away.
As the shade so gently sways.
Sing a lullaby for the
battle scars of yesterday.
It's cotton candy.
Would you look at that?
It means we're approaching the
edge of Big Mom's territory.
Keep going!
Just a bit more and we'll
be out of Toto Land.
Mama's on her way.
What a day!
Wearing borrowed smiles from those Who
traded their humanity Twisted lies like
vines that wind so gently around me Songs
that you sing thus so sweetly So look,
oh God?
Mama sings the passage for this
cruel tragedy For all her family
The prince from a fairy tale
Princess in a word of fear
The puppets show for
certain Hiding tears behind
the curtain With a sweet
nectar that draws us
with its flavor Hides a wickedness that's
difficult to Cipher Tempting
candy laid out grandly
Rots your soul like a
cavity Made in feelings
locked away And only
caused his breath
In someone else's place
Out of the candy queen
There's no room here for
machine If you want to be free
Fish and karate in
technique Vagabond drill
Just a bit more.
Hold the line until Luffy and his crew
are out, and then we can fall back!
What happened to the Straw Hats?
No way yet for their units in pursuit!
I'm afraid that we may have lost them!
We'll find them!
Once they cross the border,
we're screwed! Now go! Go! Go!
You know the drill pudding
use your acting chops to
make that fool fall head over
heels for you You can count
on me mama think of yourself
as a doll under my control
pudding Because that's
exactly what you are my dear
Mama i'm not a doll
But then let's get married
Yeah right You'll just be
horrified like all the rest
You're my daughter but that eye
still freaks me out It's the eye!
Very mean.
You sound just like a little.
You're really creeping me out.
What a weirdo!
That's so mean.
No one more left me.
A disgusting freak.
You'll run away too.
As soon as you learn what I am.
Take a good look, Sanji.
Let's see how you feel.
When you see my hideous.
Third eye.
Beautiful.
To think that you would hide that?
Time to start begging.
If I had to fake marry
someone, I'm glad it was you.
Please don't cry.
Sanji, dear.
Could you do me a favor?
Pudding, where are you going?
Didn't you have a favor to ask of me?
Pedal Spedal!
Are you even there?
Tell me if Mama's with you. Damn it.
Come to your, sir.
There's a call from Cacao Island. Huh?
It's a report from the
territory slug at the border.
Well, spit it out.
They're alerting us of passage.
The Straw Hat ship has
left Totoland coordinates.
Go back to your ships, Germa.
Mission accomplished.
About time.
Understood.
Loud and clear.
Germa has retreated.
Bring them back!
I didn't want to see you lose.
Especially not with
your back to the ground.
You were on your stomach
the first time you fell.
Why did you get up just
to land on your back?
I wonder why, too.
But Barrel, the whole I never put my back
on the ground rumor, it held no truth.
It was all a lie.
Yeah, I realize that.
I've witnessed it through the mirrors.
I know what you've been doing.
Pretending to be invincible and perfect.
All for our sake, right?
Ah!
Mm-hmm.
Katakuri, you could make friends
if you covered that big old mouth.
This is me.
If anyone laughs, then
I'll just beat him up.
Oh, a pelican heel. Huh?
They can walk out my head.
Hmm.
You better run.
Gah!
Oh, no! Help her!
There's so much blood!
This is messed up!
What's the matter? It's awful!
Barrel got hurt really bad!
She what? Barrel!
Who did this?
I'll be okay.
But you're bleeding from the head.
Tell me, how did this happen?
All those dumb jerks you beat up
took it out on Barrel as revenge.
That's not fair.
It's not her fault.
Damn it.
It wasn't supposed to turn out like this.
Big Brother.
Don't worry.
It's not too bad.
Forget those jerks.
You're fine just the way you are.
Stop it. You fool.
Hell was hurt because of me.
Because I was too soft.
I knew you'd come, stupid eel.
About time we've been expecting you. Huh?
What's that crap around your neck?
You'll pay for what you
did to my sister's face!
I'll never let my guard down ever again!
I'll teach you the meaning of true fear!
Pulley.
Hm?
Have a Straw Hat.
Do you really want to know?
I'm sure you'll be relieved to hear it.
So you can see ahead into the future too.
He just left our territory.
I won't forgive him, you know!
Not after what he did to you today?
I knew it.
Luffy's far past the border by now.
It's time to go!
Alright, Gemma Double Six.
Fall back now!
Fire, fire!
Don't let a single one of them get away!
She's coming for us.
It's her!
Soul poke us.
When selfish words can hold us.
You're lured by a cake slice.
Though it's better to think twice.
Soon enough you'll see how
much that you must sacrifice.
There's no gain here.
Power reigns here.
All is ruled by fear.
Bring a treat here.
Make it sweet, dear.
Or you'll find your end is quite near.
Tempting candy.
Laid out grandly.
Berets your soul.
Like a cavity.
Soul focus.
Chef like a croak.
Mama.
Give your lifespan and breath.
So don't pass.
This is the queen's last song.
The choice is yours, life or death.
With the powerful forces
of the Sun Pirates
and Gemma Double Six guarding their backs,
the Straw Hats make their escape at last.
The Sunny, now leaving the
Emperor Big Mom's territory,
presses on towards its next adventure.
Hey, maybe I can make you
all something? Dinner?
Oh, please!
I'm not doing this!
I'm just dying of hunger!
I can't even help!
It's delicious!
How'd you get by while I was gone?
Please, tell me you ate.
Shortly after, in the East Blue...
Where the hell's my meal? It's coming!
Chef Zeff, why are we tolerating this?
Let's take them out!
These juts are our enemies.
I'll take care of it.
Just stay out of my way.
Come on, what's the hold-up, huh?
They're really pushing their luck.
All right, all right.
People get hungry every hour of the day.
Even the bad guys need to eat.
Now, dig in.
If you're hungry, then I'll feed you.
We'll settle the rest later.